<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Home Office Politics | Make Money Save Money in 2021</title>
    <link href="https://homeofficepolitics.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://homeofficepolitics.com" />
    <updated>2021-04-16T12:48:24-06:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Staff</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://homeofficepolitics.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Make Money</title>
        <author>
            <name>Staff</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://homeofficepolitics.com/make-money/"/>
        <id>https://homeofficepolitics.com/make-money/</id>
            <category term="Make Money"/>

        <updated>2021-04-15T23:12:41-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://homeofficepolitics.com/media/posts/9/make-money-entrepreneur-960.png" alt="Entrepreneur Side Hustle Work from Home" />
                     This is a static page focused around the pillar "make money", and will be a manually-written page that highlights all the topic clusters and articles about making money. 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>About Us</title>
        <author>
            <name>Staff</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://homeofficepolitics.com/about/"/>
        <id>https://homeofficepolitics.com/about/</id>
            <category term="About"/>

        <updated>2021-04-16T07:54:06-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://homeofficepolitics.com/media/posts/1/about-home-office-politics-960-50.jpg" alt="About Home Office Politics" />
                     We've been working online since 2002. We begun doing technical support and design services for an early ecommerce platform. Our first full-time work from home gig started in 2011 and we've been doing this ever since. We now manage five brands with a few dozen contractors. We've always thought we should chronicle our lives and experience working from home. We've had challenges, fun times, and love the puns all along the way. Follow us and we'll introduce you to how you can work from home on your own side hustle, time gig working for someone else, and save money too. 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>About You</title>
        <author>
            <name>Staff</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://homeofficepolitics.com/about-you/"/>
        <id>https://homeofficepolitics.com/about-you/</id>
            <category term="Resources"/>

        <updated>2021-04-15T23:10:42-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://homeofficepolitics.com/media/posts/2/about-you.jpg" alt="About You Working From Home" />
                     We want to know more about you. Tell us what you want to achieve? Do you want to make more more money, save money, start a side hustle or get side gig? What challenges are you experiencing? What would help you achieve these goals? If we can help, we will get back to you with more information and resources. Loading…
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Contact Us</title>
        <author>
            <name>Staff</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://homeofficepolitics.com/contact/"/>
        <id>https://homeofficepolitics.com/contact/</id>
            <category term="About"/>

        <updated>2021-04-16T12:48:24-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://homeofficepolitics.com/media/posts/3/contact-hop-960.png" alt="Contact Home Office Politics" />
                     Send us an email by completing the form below. No spam please. Loading… 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Terms, Conditions, Privacy, etc.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Staff</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://homeofficepolitics.com/tcp/"/>
        <id>https://homeofficepolitics.com/tcp/</id>
            <category term="About"/>

        <updated>2021-04-15T23:12:51-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://homeofficepolitics.com/media/posts/6/terms-conditions-privacy.jpg" alt="Home Office Politics Terms, Conditions Privacy Policies" />
                     Terms of Service Our service is provided as-is with no warranty. We will do our best to provide you great information and tools and keep them available as much as possible. We reserve the right to limit access to our resources at our sole discretion.&nbsp; We reserve the right to use the content, data and tools at our disposal for our advantage as long as it is good and legal. Disclosure The&nbsp;content on HomeOfficePolitics.com may contain affiliate links, meaning we&nbsp;receive payment if you decide to make a purchase or sign up through our links, at no cost to you. Please use our links to help support everything we are trying to do for you and our community. 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Save Money</title>
        <author>
            <name>Staff</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://homeofficepolitics.com/save-money/"/>
        <id>https://homeofficepolitics.com/save-money/</id>
            <category term="Save Money"/>

        <updated>2021-04-16T07:50:20-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://homeofficepolitics.com/media/posts/8/save-money-960-50.jpg" alt="Save Money" />
                     Manual pillar page about the pillar keyword ... e.g Save Money. Includes a manually updated or written description of the cluster topics and articles contained in the "save money" pillar. 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Write for Us</title>
        <author>
            <name>Staff</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://homeofficepolitics.com/write-for-us/"/>
        <id>https://homeofficepolitics.com/write-for-us/</id>
            <category term="About"/>

        <updated>2021-04-16T07:47:23-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://homeofficepolitics.com/media/posts/4/write-for-hop-960.png" alt="Write for us" />
                     We love working with other authors and people experienced with making money, saving money, working from home, remote jobs, side hustles, side gigs and personal finance. Please complete this form if you have something you would like to contribute or if you want to work together. We love reciprocating links, articles, etc. Fees may apply. Don't get overwhelmed here, this is more common sense and is easy if you write quality content. Submit your content. Thank you. 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
</feed>
